<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Graham Park's Blog</title><link>https://grahamjpark.com/blog/rss.xml</link><description>Writings from Graham about whatever happens to be on his mind</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 23:03:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><image><url>https://grahamjpark.com/assets/gp_small_new.png</url><title>GP Logo</title><link>https://grahamjpark.com/blog/all-posts.html</link></image><item><title>Four Ways to Respond to The Social Dilemma</title><link>https://grahamjpark.com/blog/social-dilemma.html</link><description>I just finished watching The Social Dilemma. While the film does a good job explaining the issues technology is facing, it doesn’t equip you with how to respond. As someone who has been passionate about these issues for a while, I wanted to share some easy ways you can respond. Digital Minimalism by...</description><author>Graham Park</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 22:07:32 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://grahamjpark.com/blog/social-dilemma.html</guid></item><item><title>How to Streamline Your Job Search</title><link>https://grahamjpark.com/blog/job-search-tips.html</link><description>I officially started my job with Virtual Peaker a couple of months ago. I’m fortunate to have found such a perfect fit. I know many people are looking to make the next step in their career or land their first job, so I wanted to share my tips and techniques for finding and researching job opportuni...</description><author>Graham Park</author><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 21:07:13 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://grahamjpark.com/blog/job-search-tips.html</guid></item><item><title>Creating a Static Blog Generator</title><link>https://grahamjpark.com/blog/site-generator.html</link><description>Recently I went about revamping my personal site. After recreating my homepage, I decided I wanted to add a blog to it. Below you’ll find an overview of my approach and an explanation of how I created a short python script to do the job. I'm not going to list every detail, but you can all the code...</description><author>Graham Park</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:15:36 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://grahamjpark.com/blog/site-generator.html</guid></item><item><title>My security suggestions</title><link>https://grahamjpark.com/blog/security-suggestions.html</link><description>I find myself recommending things to my friends a lot (sometimes it’s even because they asked me for my recommendations!), and I get a lot of enjoyment out of recommending things I love. So I decided I wanted to create a series of posts about things I like to endorse. Given my background working in...</description><author>Graham Park</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">https://grahamjpark.com/blog/security-suggestions.html</guid></item></channel></rss>